<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>DIY on Cakes By Cassidy</title>
    <link>https://cakesbycassidy.github.io/tags/diy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in DIY on Cakes By Cassidy</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy 2022 Cassidy Belk</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cakesbycassidy.github.io/tags/diy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>5 Ways to Bake Healthier</title>
      <link>https://cakesbycassidy.github.io/blog/5waystobakehealthier/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cakesbycassidy.github.io/blog/5waystobakehealthier/</guid>
      <description>section.container img { width: 400px; }  If you have been trying to watch what you eat or are trying to cut back on certain foods, then I am here to help! We have all fallen victim to midnight munchies, and sometimes nothing sounds better than some freshly baked brownies. But just because you got a chocolate craving doesn’t mean you have to sacrifice all your hard and healthy work you have been putting in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Allergy Free Desserts For Everyone to Enjoy</title>
      <link>https://cakesbycassidy.github.io/blog/allergyfreedesserts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cakesbycassidy.github.io/blog/allergyfreedesserts/</guid>
      <description>section.container img { width: 400px; }  There is nothing worse than going to an event and realizing that you can’t eat any of the desserts because they aren’t gluten free or allergen free. This is something I go through every holiday or occasion. It doesn’t upset me much anymore, but it would be nice to get to a party for once and be greeted by a gluten free cupcake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Treat Yourself to These Christmas Desserts</title>
      <link>https://cakesbycassidy.github.io/blog/treatyourselftochristmasdesserts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cakesbycassidy.github.io/blog/treatyourselftochristmasdesserts/</guid>
      <description>section.container img { width: 400px; }  With the holidays fast approaching, I thought it’d be a great idea to share with you two of my family’s favorite Christmas desserts. It is so important to come together during the holidays and spend time with your loved ones making everlasting memories. During this busy time of year I look for simple and easy ideas that will both bring the holiday spirit into my home- while remaining as hassle free as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
